Howard Gillette Collection on the Italian American Community of Washington, D.C., 1980-1986 MS2072
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Metzeroth, Lucille M. Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company worker, undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Mezzanotte, Ferrer (Frank). News vendor. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Migliaccio, Joseph. Fruit vendor and founder of the Sons of Italy. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Milice, Angela. Justice Department employee, undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Miller, Frank. Printer for The Star, undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Monaldo family. Biaglo was a pastry chef. Frank L. was a shoemaker. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Moretti, Constance Messina. Volunteer. Annunciation church, undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Morigi, Roger. This folder contains information on skilled Italian construction workers in the D.C. area, undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Moses, John G. Lieutenant colonel, undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Musolino, Dominic Joseph. Gas station owner, undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Natoli, Joseph. Grocer and Car Dealer. Our Lady of Sorrows, undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Nencioni, Lucia. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Nicastro family. Includes index cards and photographs, one of which is of altar boys., undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Nicholas, Julie James. Boyfriend killed her accidentally with a gun he claimed he did not know was loaded, undated (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Niederlehner, Kurt. Banquet captain, undated (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Niosi family. Grocers. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Ofano, Amelia. Widow of barber, undated (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Orcino family. Owned Avignone Freres. Lido Civil Club, undated (Box 5, Folder 70)
- Pagi, Dante. Barber, undated (Box 5, Folder 71)
- Palumbo family. Shoe repair. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 5, Folder 72)
- Pappa, Giuseppe. Security guard, undated (Box 5, Folder 73)
- Pappano family. Dry cleaners and Italian festival organizers. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 5, Folder 74)
- Parreco, Edward. Partner of James Parreco & Son Inc., family excavation and construction firm, undated (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Pasqualicchio, Leonard. Realtor, undated (Box 5, Folder 76)
- Pasquini, Mary Theresa Italiana. Branch secretary for D.C. Department of Human Resources, undated (Box 5, Folder 77)
- Pavlos family. Nick, an electrician, died in an on-the job accident. Penagiota Zogas Pavlos was the widow of a radio repair show owner, undated (Box 5, Folder 78)
- Payne, Mark Edward. Funeral home attendant, undated (Box 5, Folder 79)
- Peluso, Alphonso. Barber. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 5, Folder 80)
- Peona, Francesca. Citizenship paper, undated (Box 5, Folder 81)
- Perna family. Lived in Tenleytown, undated (Box 5, Folder 82)
- Petrini, Aldo. Catholic priest. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 5, Folder 83)
- Petronella, D. (Penny) St. John. Active in Republican Women's Club, undated (Box 5, Folder 84)
- Pezzuti, Mary. Widow of hotel employee. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 5, Folder 85)
- Pirrone, Antonio J. Shoe repair. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 5, Folder 86)
- Pisapia, Louis. Food Broker, undated (Box 5, Folder 87)
- Pizza family. Grocers. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 5, Folder 88)
- Policelli, Rosalie Gentilcore. Dry Cleaner. HOLY ROSARY family, undated (Box 5, Folder 89)
- Polito family. Alice V. was the wife of a dry cleaner. Anthony Junior was a tile setter, undated (Box 5, Folder 90)
- Pomponio family. Index card, undated (Box 5, Folder 91)
- Prada, Arnold G. Owned heating, air conditioning and refrigeration firm, undated (Box 5, Folder 92)
- Preller, Francis. Engineer, undated (Box 5, Folder 93)
- Prencipe family, undated (Box 5, Folder 94)
- Pucci, Frank. Index card, undated (Box 5, Folder 95)
- Puglisi, Carmelo. Barber. Fiumedinisi, undated (Box 5, Folder 96)
- Puliatti, Joseph. Construction worker, undated (Box 5, Folder 97)
- Range, Heidi Lois. College student and cancer victim, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Raynor, Margaret F. Legal secretary, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Reeves, Rose Anne Panella., undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Ricciardi, Agnes M. Congressional liaison officer with the Veterans administration, Annunciation member and Republican volunteer, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Riley, Nora. Partial photocopy of obituary, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Rinaldi family., undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Rogers, Gordon B. Lieutenant general and cavalry officer, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Romeo, Carmela Motta. Active in orphan affairs. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Rousopoulos, Peter. Restaurateur, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Rowe, E. Romayne. Civil Service Commission examiner and investigator, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Ruggieri, Nick. Owned Nick's Valet. Fiumedinisi, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Rumbough, William. General and World War II signal officer, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Ruppert, Katherine C. Veterans Administration employee and Red Cross volunteer, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Russ, Martha Louise. Bureau of National affairs employee, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Saia, Pasquale Frank. Made sandals for Franciscans, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Saylor, Margaret. Taught Italians who lived in her area, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Sandro, Sandi. Housekeeper at HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Santini, Anthony P. Meat Marker owner, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Santucci, Ferruccio. Stone mason, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Sapienza, Mrs. Pietro C. Widow of cobbler. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Savage, Winifred M. Austin. Widow, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Scafetta family., undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Scaldaferri, Frank. Stone mason, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Scalessa, C.F., M.D. Pediatrician:, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Schmidt, John R. Catholic monisignor, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Sciacco, James. Installation foreman for Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Scuderi, Placido. Stockbroker. World War II veteran, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Segreti family. Stone masons. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Sergi, Sebastiano. Tailor. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Simi family. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Sirica, John. Judge, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Skiados. Partial obituary photocopy; deceased was a nurse, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Smith. Albert C. Smith was an embassy clerk. Helen Hunter Smith was his widow and co-owner of Hunter's Tavern in Upper Marlboro, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Sorge, Joseph F. Owned hotel barbershop, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Spadaro, Dominic. Index card, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Sparacino, Charles. Barber. Fiumedinisi, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Stathopovlos, Nick G. Greek, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Statler, Esther Mc Murray, R.N. Navy and Veterans Administration nurse, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
- St. Clair, Lloyd Dale. Service advisor for Community Auto Service. Killed in automobile accident, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Stefanelli, Joseph (Jack). Stefanelli Brothers Tile Company, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Stone, Leonard J. Manager of international projects for International Telephone and Telegraph Corporation's Washington office, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Streit, Paul H. Army major, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Sullivan, John S. colonel. Partial photocopy of obituary, undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Tamagni, Augie. Dental technician, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Tana family. Barber, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Teti, Nicholas. Jeweler, undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Thon, George J. Managed Forest Lake apartments, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Timpe, George. Catholic priest. Partial photocopy of obituary, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Toftoy, Holter N. Army general, undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Travaglini, Edmund. Dentist, undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Trivelli, Carmela. Widow of barber, undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Troost, Veronika, M.D. Physician, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Trotta, Rose L. Bureau of Engraving and Printing clerk. Carmelite Sisters Club, undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Turturro, Agostino. General Services Administration landscaper, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Urciolo family, undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Vaccaro family, undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Vasaio family, undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Valenti, Alfonso. Barber, undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Veneziani. Partial photocopy. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Verdi, J.S. Index card, undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Vidi family. HOLY ROSARY, undated (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Villatico, Mary G. Baker and restaurateur, undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Volland, Roberta. Active in colonial American societies, undated (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Wade, Margaret C. Joyce. Democratic club officer, undated (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Weeda, Joseph G, undated (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Wheeler, Charles, undated (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Whitsell Howard E. (Whitey), undated (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Willard, Ira. Partial photocopy of obituary, undated (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Wiliging, Eugene P. Catholic University librarian, undated (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Williams, Daniel James. Leukemia victim, undated (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Wolford. Staff sergeant in the Air Force. Partial photocopy of obituary, undated (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Yankey, Kay A. British embassay employee, undated (Box 6, Folder 72)
- Zagami family, undated (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Zerega family. Restaurateurs, undated (Box 6, Folder 74)
- Ziccardi, Michael J. Plumber, undated (Box 6, Folder 75)
- Photo proofs, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Photo proofs and negatives, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Photo proofs and negatives, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Photo proofs and negatives, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Photo proofs and negatives, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Photo proofs and negatives, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Two 5 x 7 photo negatives, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Photo proof and negatives, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Photo proofs and negatives, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Photo proofs and negatives, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Photo proofs and negatives, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Photo negative and photograph, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Italian photographs, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Photo negatives and photographs, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)